Praise the Lord. Praise the Lord.
>> Um, it's such a joy to be here.
Uh, when I when I came here in the
morning,
I just saw the faithfulness of God.
You know, there are things you look at
in life
and you're humbled by what God can do.
And we give him all the glory. Amen. And
I know that this is the beginning of
many beginnings. And my prayer is that
we shall be found faithful and worthy
even to do his work and assignment. I
want to appreciate all the pastors that
are here. Minister Bish, may God bless
you. Pastor Eugene and your wife. May
God bless you. Pastor Ken Jou, I saw
your wife. I know he's with the boys.
May God bless you. Pastor Peter Kjagua
with your wife. God bless you. Pastor
Negoa with your wife William. God bless
you. Pastor Anita. Hallelujah. Soon and
very soon we'll be saying with your
husband. God bless you. Amen. Uh pastor
Jerro Kevin with your wife. May God
bless you Pastor Lee. Hallelujah. May
God bless you. Even you now soon and
very soon we'll be seeing with your
husband. Hallelujah. Amen.
Um, I also want to appreciate my wife uh
who is dealing with
my boy or our boy. If you're a mother of
boys, congratulations.
They know how to take care of their
mothers.
Uh, I want us to continue
with the cardinal laws of revival.
Cardinal laws of revival.
The Lord has been speaking a lot to me
concerning this matter. Yesterday night
was quite heavy. I slept quite late
trying to download some realities from
Zion.
We are
we are mining
these truths
from uh from the story of first kings.
Let me go there.
First kings
We are getting it from first kings 18
beginning from verse 30 all the way to
40.
The points that I'm giving the eight
cardinal laws of revival are coming from
this particular portion of scripture.
Then Elijah said to all the people,
"Come near to me." So all the people
came near to him and he repaired the
altar of the Lord that was broken. And
we handled that point. We saw that he
never re he never built a new altar, but
he repaired the altar. And that
introduces the first law, which is the
law of patterns and systems. And we said
last Sunday that there is nothing new
that we can do other than build on the
foundation that Jesus has already laid
according to 1 Corinthians 3 and:1. So
we need to locate if we need to see the
fire of God again, we need to locate the
abandoned systems and abandoned patterns
because our God functions under patterns
and systems. And that's where we got the
point. Look at the next one.
Uh, and Elijah took 12 stones according
to the number of the tribes of the sons
of Jacob to whom the word of the Lord
had come saying, "Israel shall be your
name." He took the 12 stones. Then with
the stone he built an altar. So what
what is the what is the language of um
repairing the altar? So we have you
locate the abandoned altar. Then
repairing the altar is the language of
the law of reformation. And last Sunday
we took time we understood about some of
the historical reformers that showed up
in history. One of them being Martin
Luther and reformation is still
happening even now. Reformation is
returning the church back to its
original formation.
If we need the power, the fire, the
manifestation of the glory of the early
church, you need the doctrine and the
and the assembly of the early church.
The future of the church is always on
its past. And uh today we are going to
look at the law of divine timing. The
law of divine timing. Look at the next
one. With a stone he built an altar in
the name of the Lord. And he made a
trench around the altar large enough to
hold two ses of seed. There is a reason
why that happened. And he put the wood
in altar, cut the bull in pieces and
laid it on the wood and said, "Fill four
water pots with water. Pour it on the
burn sacrifice and on the wood." Don't
worry, that's a drumist. Then he said,
"Do it a second time." And they did it a
second time. And he said, "Do it at that
time." And they did it at that time. So
the water ran all around the altar, and
he also filled the trench with water.
And it came to pass
at the time of the offering of the
evening sacrifice that Elijah the
prophet came near and said, "Lord, God
of Abraham, Isaac, and Israel, let it be
known this day that you are God in
Israel, and I am your servant, and I
have done all these things." Now, look
at what the Bible says. And it came to
pass at the time.
It came to pass at the time of what?
At the time of
the evening sacrifice.
My notes are all scattered.
May God give me grace. This this is
going to be heavy. So when it came at
the time of the evening sacrifice,
Elijah came near and said, "Lord God of
Abraham, Isaac and Israel, in this
story, there are almost four laws that
are here, and I I believe God that
possibly we might be able to handle
them." In this story, you find the law
of time. You find the law of divine
sequence and protocol. And you also find
the law of covenant in that portion of
scripture.
But let me begin with the law of divine
time or the law of divine timing. The
things of God are programmed in time.
The things of God are programmed in
time.
Any activity
that concerns God and man is scheduled
in time.
Any activity that concerns God and man
is always programmed or scheduled in
time.
God lives out of time, but man lives in
time. So whatever God wants to do to
man,
he must visit time
to make sure that what he has appointed
for man is programmed and delivered in
time.
So
God is not disadvantaged by time because
he lives in eternity where time does not
count. So man is the entity that lives
in time and man is advantaged or
disadvantage by time. When man does not
know
what God is doing in what time, he will
be disadvantaged.
Look at the book of Luke 19 and verse
44.
Luke 19 and verse 44. Jesus is concerned
about the children of Israel. He comes
and rebukes them and tells them, "You
have the ability to look at the skies
and discern
and discern. Luke Luke 19 and verse 44.
Is this Luke 19? Okay. Yeah. And your
children within you to the ground and
they will not leave you in one stone
upon another because you did not know
the time of your visitation. Look at let
me give you another scripture. I want to
tie them together. That that is Luke
19:44.
Luke 19:44.
Look at the book of Matthew 16 verse 2
and verse3. Matthew 16:2 and verse 3.
He answered and said to them, everybody
read, "When it is evening, what do you
say? You say it will be fair weather for
the sky is red." So just just hold it
there. There are people that can look. I
remember one day I was with Pastor Kevin
and I didn't know Liuru very well but he
looked and said
this scripture is not for pastor Kevin.
I am just saying there are people who
can make predictions of weather by just
studying the skies. And there was a
breed of the Jews who had that ability.
And now the Lord begins to rebuke them.
In the next verse, see what he tells
them that you guys have the ability to
look upon the heavens. And in the
morning it will be fall weather today.
For the sky is red and threatening.
Hypocrates, you know how to design the
face of the sky. But you cannot do what?
Design what? The signs of the time.
Now when you tie this with Luke 19:44,
Jesus looks upon Jerusalem,
you can begin from Luke 19 and verse 43
and verse 44. Today we are going to read
many scriptures because I want to
establish a matter. Luke 19 and verse 43
and then verse 44. Luke 19 43 and 44.
For days will come upon you when your
enemies will build an embarkment around
you, surround you and close you on every
side. See what the Lord is saying. And
level you and your children within you
to the ground and they will not live in
you one stone upon another because you
did not know the time of your
visitation.
Now this is the scripture when Jesus was
born.
He was meant to come and deliver the
house of Israel.
But the children of Israel did not
receive him as their Messiah.
Neither did they receive him as their
savior. And Jesus is making a prophecy
of the disadvantage
of what will happen because they have
missed their time.
So he's looking at the children of
Israel and he's saying according to the
programs of eternity, I was scheduled to
come at this time to bring salvation
first to the household of Israel. But
they are the ones planning on executing
me. So what has Israel missed the time
of their visitation?
That was a moment in eternity where God
had ordained to visit man. But man was
not aware. The antenance of discernment
could not pick the frequencies of
eternity to understand the programs, the
agendas and the assignment of heaven.
What did they do? They crucified him.
And because they missed the timings of
God, there were consequences
for doing that. And part of that
consequence was judgment over Jerusalem.
70 AD. The Romans went and surrounded
Jerusalem.
68 AD they surrounded it. They besieged
it for two years. In 70 AD there was
war. The Romans massacred.
It was a holocaust. More than 4 million
Jews. The the D in history is
staggering. And this is when Jesus said,
"If you are found on the mountains,
don't return to Jerusalem. It will be a
bad day for the nursing mothers and
pregnant women because he knew the
judgment that will come because of not
embracing him. Look at the consequences
of that missing up to date they are
still waiting for the Messiah.
So when we are talking matters revival
if there are prophecies concerning a
land that in a certain time frame there
will be moves of God a thousand years
later if Jesus tries Kenya can still
suffer because of missing that move.
Am I speaking to anyone?
Because God operates under certain
timings. There are certain divine
schedules,
programs.
I was looking at Kenya and I was saying
what if revival will be our solution,
not mando.
If it doesn't come, we might be
perpetually
on the streets.
Because what was meant to heal the land,
it was prophesied. But there was no one
sensitive enough. There were no heralds
to run with the prophecy and push it
until implementation.
Someone told me this country was listed
among the nations that will default
their loans. South Africa being one of
them. Kenya was also listed. And if we
were we would have defaulted the loan,
the dollar right now will be at 260. $1
at 260h
me I'm crying for revival. I don't know
about you
because I know it has been announced.
I I've been studying the prophecies of
the land just to understand because
anytime you see a certain movement of
men, you need to interrocate it. Is it
that there was supposed to be a
preceding movement that another movement
has preceded the movement? You need to
interrogate it.
And so Jesus looks upon Jerusalem. He's
he's broken. He knows what is going to
befall Jerusalem. It is an irreversible
reality. And he looks upon them and
says, "You know what? This is going to
be a bad day because you have missed the
time of your visitation. You have missed
the schedule time that was meant to
shift your season as a nation and
transform you to a nation that will not
have suffered as Jesus being the
Messiah.
Can I go further?
You see, the Lord wanted to use Israel
as a model nation, a nation under God.
He wanted to use Israel as a sample
nation and what that nation can look
like when a nation submits under God.
See what they told God. We want kings
like other nations. So they never knew
their identity and they began to desire
to be like the heathenistic nations that
did not have a god like their god. And
the Lord now decided that this nation is
not ready for my agenda. Guess what? The
Lord has not shifted his mind. The Lord
chose another entity. It is called the
church.
Now in our day, the Lord wants to show
the world how a man under God can be.
But the men that are in Christianity,
they are two-fitted. One leg in the
world, one leg in the church.
The same way Israel missed the
opportunity to express all the realities
of heaven is the same way the church is
missing the opportunity to express the
realities of heaven.
We will come to the gates of Hades and
the triumphing church and begin to see
the kind of church Jesus was looking at.
So when we go back now to
when we go back to
the book of Kings, when we go back to
Kings,
we begin to see something that is very
powerful
in Kings.
The Bible says now go back uh from verse
2 Kings 18 from verse 32. Please tell
your neighbor, neighbor, I prophesy to
you, you will not miss the time of your
visitation.
Whatever God has ordained for you in
time, you will not miss it. Are we
together? That's why you can go to a
meeting and that was the meeting to
connect you to your time of visitation.
you because sometimes God will send a
prophet to you or send you to a prophet.
Encounters encounters are products of
collusion between humanity and divinity
and anytime that collusion happens the
life of a man can never be the same. You
cannot collude with eternity and remain
the same in the real of men. The pattern
in scripture is very clear. A shepherd
is at the back of the mountain looking
after his father-in-law sheep. the next
thing he meets God as a burning bush. He
goes back straight as a deliverer. There
are certain timings that God has set
over your life. And that's why you need
to fight for anything that distracts
you.
Relationships,
things that are looking like they are
taking your focus from where you're
going. Anything that tries to mess you
up. There is something I saw when the
devil cannot attack you directly, he
will sponsor an environment for
selfdestruction.
Psychiatrist will call it depression
that is suicidal.
Um medical people will call it
addictions. But if you look deeper, it
is what we call a possibility of
self-destruction.
There is a real you must look at
something and you know this is not an
addiction. This is a demonic tool in my
hand to selfdestroy me.
Am I speaking to anyone?
You you see we have we have socialized
the church and one of the attacks in the
church is to make sure that we enter the
realm of humanism and socialism and lose
spiritualism.
Okay.
So sometimes we look at matters with
human eyes,
social eyes. There has been a debate of
what is 666?
Is it a number in the past? Is it a
number in the present?
But when you look at the number six is
the creation of man.
looks like it is an age men will enter
in their head. There will be perfected
humanism.
It's now in the curriculum and what we
are studying. What we are perfecting is
humanism.
Whatever is going to replace
Christianity in nations is not a more
superior teaching, it is humanism.
People trying to reason life cuz even
those who believe in the theories of
creation, they don't even understand it.
But there is a humanistic nature just to
to come and say the gospel is a lie. And
I believe that's why uh the whole thing
666 before it becomes a number on your
fairhead, it will become a reality in
your head.
Ah
the timings of God.
So what does I don't know why I feel
like I'm struggling with my mic. I don't
know what you're going to do. So what
does um Elijah know?
Elijah understands. You see the
protocols of Elijah. He gathers men to
Mount Kaml. Hey guys, come prophets of
Bal. He that calls the meeting runs the
meeting. So this was not the meeting of
the prophets of Bal. This was the
meeting of Elijah.
And they did a wrong thing when they
came.
A friend of mine was preaching in a
certain territory full of people that
never believed in Christianity.
And you know these are violent men in
this town. They were violent men. They
will have those debates and say you know
Jesus is not God and he was an an
intercessor and a man of prayer. And he
got mad. One day he found the arguments
and he said you know what let us not
argue. If Jesus is not God, then um I
will convert to your faith. He said,
"Bring me seven heavy brothers and let
them stand." And then he he he lined
them up and he took 10 steps back.
So he was 10 step back and he lifted his
hand. He said, "This is what is going to
happen. I will pray in the name of Jesus
and the power of that name will slay
these men. Those men were not believers.
They were brought by the men of the
other community. Now what they did not
know, the more they were obeying his
instruction, the more they were entering
his environment.
So he said 10 men they brought. Stand
there. They stood. Lift up your hands
they lifted. He knew now you are under
my power.
And the man was very wise. In his
prayer, he began to preach. Father, in
the name of Jesus, you are the only God.
All the other gods are in the graves. He
mentioned their names. So and so is in
the grave. So and so is in the grave. We
know they in the grave, but you're
alive. Now touch. They fell. He said,
"Bring them back." Second service,
he prayed again. preach about Jesus
touch they fell that service
he now told them it is time to convert
because it is automatic he's not God
and of course you know there was they
were mad and his life was in danger and
they began to come to his house like
Nicodemus converting one by one
now Elijah was in charge of the
There is something Elijah one there is
an abandoned altar in the mountains of
camel. Number two,
as they gather, you you you remember
this festival was the the the prophets
of Bah raised their altar. They were
there. They were chanting. They were
cutting themselves. They were doing all
these things. And Elijah will come and
tell them, "Maybe your God has gone for
a susu break. Wait for him to come out
of the of the of the lavatories and
come. Maybe your God is asleep mocking
their God." But when the time came, when
the time of the evening sacrifice came,
the Bible says the man drew close to his
altar because he understood before when
these men were doing their rituals. If I
was to make a prayer, heaven will not
have responded. I must know the timings
and the schedules of heaven to know how
I need to reciprocate. The Bible says
when the hour of the offering of of
oblition of the evening sacrifice came,
that's when he told them, "Stop your
nonsense. Let me now show you how we do
business in this kingdom." He drew
closer to his altar. Do you understand
the schedules and the times of heaven
concerning your life?
And guess what? The evening sacrifice
was not a sacrifice of burnt offering.
You look at the Bible, the altar Elijah
built
has never been built and there has never
be anyone who raised an altar like
Elijah.
The the we will come to the place of
system and protocol. An altar entailed
12 uncut stones,
wood laid on it and a sacrifice. There
is no altar where men dug trenches and
poured water. I have read this book from
cover to cover. Nowhere in the Bible an
altar like that of Elijah was made.
And then he told them come and pour
water three times.
No, three gallons. Let's look at it.
Go go go up there. Go up there. There's
a pattern I want to lay here.
the previous scripture in the name of
the Lord. And he made a trench around
the altar large enough to hold two sears
of seed. There is nowhere men build an
altar and dug a trench. Now look at the
next one.
And he put the wood in order, cut the
bull in pieces, and laid it on the wood.
Fill four water pots with water and pour
it on the burnt sacrifice on the wood.
When you read a prophetic book, numbers
are not for statistics. They are for
revelations.
So put the wood in order.
Lay it on the wood. Fill four water
pots,
oven vessels,
because we need water ports to heal the
land. Four is the number of creation of
the earth.
When revivals come, they come to deal
with the land.
I watched what they call the Fiji
revival, which happened in 1995.
They were harvesting fish the size of
Oman. When revival hit the land, even
the fish grew.
Their bananas were like small bananas.
The yams were small. There was healing.
The land was littered with witches.
Because when when a territory is full of
witchcraft, the heavens are shut. And
what do the heavens release? The heavens
do two things. Number one, when you
operate on an open heaven, there is
divine access. So the voice of God is
available, the power of God is
available, the presence of God is
available. So when you operate under
open heaven, when you operate under open
heaven, you receive the reigns in their
time. The former reign and the latter
reigns, they are released on their time.
So when there is witchcraft in a
territory, the heaven is shut. So there
is no divine encounter but demonic
encounters. The heavens cannot pour. So
the land is frustrated and the wealth is
compromised. That's why you go to a
territory filled with witches. Progress
and prosperity is always a question.
I was watching some things from Benin
called dancing grasses.
A spirit will get in a grass, dance and
go even to the water and come back. And
then I saw some comments asking these
people with all this spiritual power,
why can't they break poverty?
You can't change your life because the
Bible says every good and perfect gift
comes from above. James.
So there is nothing that men can hold
that never came from above. Can I even
surprise you? Whatever witches give is
stolen goods
and whatever they supply was something
meant for a believer.
There is a three level when we come to
warfare. We can have hijacked goods.
They were meant to be delivered but
because of intensity of warfare the
goods were hijacked. We can have goods
that not only were they hijacked but
they were delivered to the wrong
address. So they they were hijacked and
then you can have intercepted goods. So
the goods have not left the deliverer
but there is an interception and a
barrier for them to arrive wherever they
are. And all these are functions of
spiritual space.
So when the goods are in the wrong
hands, it automatically means they came
from above. There is nothing the devil
can give.
That's why even when now people begin
get to occultism,
freemasonry and all these orders, they
must vet who is joining
because the enemy can only transact with
your gift which came from above to
advance his agenda.
I told someone
So holy exam
the devil is transactional.
It is what are you bringing on the table
and most of the times he comes fishing
in the church because genuine gifts are
in the house. That's why you must grow
according to your grace. Don't grow
beyond your capacity. There is a real
where men are hijacked.
I was here. Fill four water pots with
water and pour it on the burn sacrifice.
Four is the number of creation. Are we
together up to there? Three is the
number of the Holy Ghost. The agent that
came to fix the earth was the Holy
Spirit. In the book of Genesis, the
spirit was hoovering over the surface of
the deep. And then the Bible says, "Let
there be and the Holy Ghost began to
implement whatever proceeded from the
mouth of Elohim." So anytime there has
to be revival, there must be a fresh
move of the spirit.
He's the one that was left as our
helper. He's the one that fixes things.
Are you see? Okay, I know this is deep
and that's why I'm going slowly. Poly
pole. So fill water pots and pour on the
B sacrifice and on the wood. The nature
of this sacrifice, whatever they call
the sacrifice of oblition,
it was a sacrifice of outpouring.
Outpouring.
That is why what men were calling the
evening sacrifice,
it did not just need something on the
altar. It needed something that can be
poured on the ground. And that is why
Elijah understood the timings of heaven
and number two the demands of that time
is one thing to know what God wants to
do in a certain time is another thing to
know the demands of that time.
Not every time is a time to pray. There
are times when God will demand you sit
and study.
Not every time is a time to study. There
are times when God will demand you sit
under mentorship and tutorship because
that is where you are going. So you
could be praying when you are meant to
be mentored.
You could be reading when you're meant
to be praying. There was a demand for
that time. The the not just an altar.
They needed also a specific sacrifice.
And that's why he said bore three times.
If the earth number four has to be
healed, it must be by the Holy Spirit.
But by this time,
I want to show you something. Just go
down there. Continue there on the wood.
Go quickly. Then he said that the second
time they did a second time. And he
said, "Do it at that time." And they did
it at that time. Continue. So the water
ran all around the altar and he also
filled the trench with water.
And it came to pass at the time of the
offering of the evening sacrifice that
Elijah the prophet came near and said,
"Oh God of Abraham, Isaac and and
Israel, let it be known this day that
you are God in Israel and I'm your
servant that I may have done all these
things at your word." Continue. Hear me,
oh Lord. Hear me that these people may
know that you are the Lord God and that
you have turned their heads back to you
again. Everybody read
school.
If your parents were here, they will be
very mad how much they have spent on you
and how you are reading. Then the fire
of the Lord fell and consumed the bans.
I want you to look at the grammar. The
fire consumed the sacrifice but the fire
licked the water.
So this demand or the the what was on
the altar as a burn sacrifice was not as
important as the water.
Why the timing? What was the timing? The
evening sacrifice. What is the evening
sacrifice? The sacrifice of oblition.
One that you pour unto God.
Now today you don't need to pour water.
You need to pour your life unto God.
There are you can never carry revival if
you have not entered the evening
sacrifice. The time to pour yourself
H
it's a serious matter.
There is a there is a real men have to
silence all the other exterior factors.
There is a real of bread
but there is a real of glory.
You see when when when God is dealt with
from the realms of a father, the father
can never move in revival is until we
change our posture and begin to deal
with him in the realms of a king and a
judge. That realm you come as a prince,
not as a child. Now the church must
mature from childhood because when when
you are dealing with children, bread and
butter is their need. But there is a
real of princes where they must be taken
to be trained for war. Because thrones
are not given to children.
So in that realm, it is beyond bread and
butter. You are in the battlefield. You
are being trained how to handle the
sword, how to ride the horse, how to
contend for the throne, how to fight for
the kingdom. In that realm, your prayers
cannot be bread and butter. Now the
enemy can make us busy. Every time we
are lacking, every time house rent,
every time but there is another realm.
When you enter that realm, this realm
settles.
So now the and and that's why now you
you realize
can I preach
>> you know
when relevant irrelevance Mr. Brazil
could deal social issues and there is a
time for social issues but it cannot be
from January to January we are dealing
with social issues. Some of the social
issues will be silenced when there is
maturity.
There are things that will make me cry a
few years back. Today when you hear them
you smile because you have also
developed stamina. You have gone through
a path of training and maturity that
those issues are no longer issues.
Can I tell you as long as you're on this
earth there will be issues. So we can
center the gospel to be issue centric.
Though there are solutions from the
gospel to sort your issues but it cannot
be the only thing you are looking for.
There is another realm when you approach
the throne of God as a prince a mature
child that can inherit the throne. That
is the realm God can entrust you with a
territory. But at that realm you have
poured yourself to God that it is now
God living in you. There is nothing left
of you. The more powerful you become,
the more humble men become because there
is no self.
Hallelujah.
Now when God gives you a territory, it
it is not given for free. It comes with
warfare, it comes with confrontations,
but because you know now you are dealing
with God as a king. As you are dealing
with the territory and it also comes
with rewards because when you secure the
territory,
even the wealthy men of the territory,
you have secured them. They are under
you.
Okay.
Oh,
somebody say the evening sacrifice.
>> Somebody say the evening sacrifice.
>> Please tell that neighbor, neighbor,
every
time comes with certain instructions.
But this is the advantage. The Lord will
always supply grace for every time that
you enter.
So number one we saw the law of patterns
and systems. Number two the law of
reformation that is repair the altar.
So there was ancient abandon altar
repairing the altar. Number three the
law of divine time
spiritual schedules. I want to speak
number four and this is what I'll finish
because um
I want you to go and chew on that madam.
It is called the law of divine sequence
and protocol.
The law of divine sequence and protocol.
Now go up again where now he began to
repair the altar.
the law of divine sequence and protocol.
You know we always say, "Oh, we need the
fire of Elijah. Let the God that answers
by fire. Let that God answer by fire." I
am giving you the templates of calling
fire.
It's not easy.
Then with stones
he built an altar in the name of the
Lord. Number one with stones. So
the first thing is that when you look at
the sequence and protocol, you don't
bring a sacrifice before you have
established an altar.
Neither do you lay woods before you have
brought stones.
There's a sequence.
The first one was select and cut stones
as natural as they are. Because if God
has to interfere with the affairs of
man, he needs an altar that does not
have an effort of man.
So don't shape the stones.
Leave them as natural as they are.
You don't lift an altar on a flat
ground. An altar must be above the
ground if it has to affect the ground.
Ah there are people when they want to
cast people they must make sure their
feet is not stepping the ground they
will stand at an elevated place like
Balam and begin to curse because if you
have to affect men on ground
you can't be in their same level that's
why many demonic altars are always on
high places.
You know, I've been studying
the motions spiritually
interrogating the matters of our nation.
I've been doing a spiritual diagnosis
because I stand as a priest not a
politician. So I have to give solution
from a place of priesthood. So I I must
see in the spirit. Then
I sat down with a man and he began to
give me some things. I said, "You've
just opened my eye."
You see, there is an altar under Mount
Kenya.
Mount Kenya, there's an altar there and
a very strong altar.
And people have been sacrificing. It's
not abandoned. generations after
generations sacrifice
before the man rose the one you know
defending the mountain he fasted there
40 days
and it is in public domain said I'm
inter you know I'm just uh I'm trying to
interrogate inter introspect
and I'm in prayer
I'm in prayer
in the something.
Do you know Daniel when he was
confronted in Babylon, he faced the
altar of Jerusalem?
So when someone is facing the mountain,
it's not the mountain they worshiping.
There is an altar.
>> Okay.
So I began to interrogate. I asked
this mountain.
Then I sat with a camba and he told me
you know the name Kenya is a ka name
that came from the word kia.
So Amber went and saw the mountain and
he saw the white covering
and he said
these are doves white birds because he
couldn't say white. He was trying to
say.
So he said
interpretation.
The white person could not say kia. He
said kenya.
What is kia? Is it dove?
Is white. Someone told me is the white
part of an ostrich. Something like that.
So he was trying to explain
that this was a white mountain.
Then I began to discover when we got our
independence, it is another cousin who
went there with a flag and planted it on
mo.
It's in history. He he he's the one who
endorsed our victory on that place. A
prophetic woman came and said the angel
that watches over Kenya
that is area and he said it's like he
has been bound
and so he must be released so that the
destiny of the nation can be bound.
Then I asked myself, we have a very
powerful prayer
as a national anthem,
but we took the
sound from Allah la. Are we sleeping or
worshiping?
I'm still doing my investigation.
And then someone asked me what is this
about Jenz? I told them
that was the song that took you to
power.
That was the worship atmospheric
environmental
pangu.
So
that error then was a political motion
to fight somebody. But that thing has
never been dealt with.
It's the spirit of anarchy and dishonor.
I saw children young going to school. I
didn't even know what they were saying
and they were dishonoring the king. I
said, "When did we come to a place when
we lost honor to the king?" The Holy
Spirit told me check during the election
period the previous king was also
dishonored. So a pattern was laid kings
cannot be honored. Now the next king is
suffering dishonor because a seed was
planted from the previous king.
So what is the solution? There must be a
reconciliation
for the legality to be lifted.
Otherwise, there is a legality that
endorses dishonor.
And look at the pattern. When number two
was number two, he dishonored number
one. Now number two is dishonoring.
You see when the Bible says whatever a
man seweth
>> so shall he reap but is there now now
now that dishonor because if I dishonor
in my day it shall advance in my
children you see David had a problem
with a few women Solomon had a problem
with community of women's so the thing
escalated
so if this thing is not managed. Now
>> the next level of dishonor and how many
know the Bible says honor carries a
level of longevity of life.
>> Honor your parents. That name parents
may not just mean biological even
spiritual people that have nurtured you
because when you honor them they bless
you. So you must live to see the
blessing. So if there is no honor there
is no blessing.
So there is no reason for existence.
Premature death begins to take you out.
Because I want to pray for Kenya, not
from emotions, not from persuasions, not
from cousins, but from convictions of
the Holy Ghost, knowing that, oh God, we
dishonored the first king. We repent.
Take away the spirit of dishonor from
the king of the land. Because when
children who do not even know what they
are singing look at it, it is fun to
dishonor the one in power. We are
creating a system of disobedience which
will not just affect government. It will
affect our homes.
I'll tell you the truth.
Okay, let me not say it.
Matters politics and criticizing
leaders, please do it in your bedroom.
Not when your children are there. You'll
create a pattern whereby they will see,
oh, you are criticizing the governor,
criticizing the senator. One day they
will criticize you.
One day they will form a coup in that
house.
Diet change.
Can I explain something? Yeah.
the fridge.
Then I I began to look at history.
I realized, oh, this is the generation
that banned schools.
This is the generation that be the
demonstration did not begin now, began
then.
This is the generation that was born
under free education.
When we told teachers, you can't our
children. So what did we do? We took
discipline out. You can see we are
dealing not with something that is
happening now. This thing has been
groomed over time. When they went to
high school, one of the Cers who was in
education very powerful. Some of his
videos I saw he he will go and lecture a
headmaster in front of the students and
the students will look at the headmaster
and say oh so you you are not the one to
say there is an authority. And many
schools began to disobey their
headmasters. Then high schools, guess
what happened? High schools, the
teachers were the power to can was taken
out to a point that a student would
report you to TSC for caneing them. So
what did we do? We created an
environment for anarchy. So study from
Kbaki time. Anyone who was born when
Kbaki was president is now 28 years old.
Now it that generation cannot be
governed because no one ever showed them
force. That's why when a policeman comes
with a baton, a millennial will run
away. A genzee will take away the mask
and say shoot me because I don't know
discipline. No one initiated. You
uplifted it when I entered. The matter
is deeper than what you're seeing.
So I'm still doing my diagnosis. If you
have more diagnosis, we can compare
notes so that our prayers can be
accurate. Not just bring out of emotion.
Oh Lord, save Kenya. Lord, save Kenya.
We need to repent and say, Lord, we took
away the king and we never showed a
generation direction. Remember mercy for
where we failed. Lord, we taught a
generation as lead us to dishonor power.
Lord, we failed as a generation.
Remember mercy and restore our hearts.
And then now we need to tell politicians
can we do politics that is different
>> let us honor leadership what you are
fighting for you'll get it maybe and the
pattern you have used is what
>> they will use so perpetually it will be
we have hashtags for the king we have
songs for the king
where other nations have to guard their
king
okay Am I speaking too much?
Hey,
you know in our school there in our
school when I was in form three, that is
when they stopped monolization.
So I didn't monolize anyone and I felt
bad
because I was monolized.
And guess that class that we did not
monolize, guess what they did? They
burnt the school
because that monolization used to create
an order that these are seniors and
these are juniors.
[Music]
And you see what created is that those
that are senior ought to be respected.
Of course,
but there was order in school that when
a form four came a form one will just
step aside for for to take shower and
all that.
Now you don't see that order. You'll
even see see a Sunday school child
sitting and a parent is Sunday school.
Tell your neighbor, neighbor, we need to
pray from a place of facts and not
emotions. But can I tell you something?
25th was our test mark.
Well, that day, my goodness, that day
come
that was the litmus test.
that one. If you live with intercessors,
let them tell you it was meant to be a
bloodbath. God
had mercy. Yeah.
I don't know where we'll be, but now I
can tell you going forward to Kosawa
to Kosawa. Going forward the noises will
reduce.
things will begin to shift and happen
and Kenya will take a certain trajectory
going forward. Things are looking good.
Amen. Things are looking good. That
spirit will will subsidize. But we need
to talk to our people and give them
priestly direction. If you dishonor,
expect dishonor in your day. If you
honor, expect honor. Next time don't
call a nation hustle a nation call it a
blessed nation prophesy to the nation
give it a prophetic name you remember
when they were forming jubilee very
prophetic on timing Kenya was turning 50
what did they use a symbol of abdav
peace and that was the season we faced
everything covid came we had two
elections no bloodshed because the
prophecy kept on holding the nation
Then with stones he built an altar. So
what why was I was telling you that
mountain
when you see people lift their hands and
now it has become so powerful that if
you need influence in the mountain you
must sacrifice there. The ones guarding
it are not playing jokes.
I can assure you
anyone that rises from the mountain is
not from the church. That's the reality.
That priesthood is ancient
and the frequency of their
ancient and the gers are serious.
That's why when you go towards Kanyaga,
you go towards Neri,
you realize that prayers were left for
women
because the men are guarding the altar.
And when women begin to fight
spiritually, they will even rule
physically.
Majority of the intercessors in Nakuru
are women. Look who sits on the throne.
It is a deborra pattern. If I win, the
credit will not go to a man. It shall go
to a woman.
Please don't bring your agenda card.
Priesthood
is ordained for men. That's why in towns
like Ner
many people who have tried to rise in
prayer as men they get a very serious
opposition because the pattern is
anient.
So uh I was in a meeting of our woman of
God there and she'll be coming for the
women conference.
Prophet Teswini she she has been leading
a prayer movement for women and that is
what now has been preserving their
children.
In terms of territorial preservation,
altars are not jokes.
Altars alters destinies and see and and
and lives of men. So if we don't
understand the spiritual operation of
altars, it's going to be chaotic.
The whole thing of Baragoy, how people
fight there, the the the scandal is
beyond stealing goats and sheep.
That thing there is an ancient altar in
that town.
Those cattle rusters before they go for
any operation, they have a priest that
must anoint them, ordain them and bless
them.
which um one of the sons in the house
used to be a policeman there and he told
me pastor I'm telling you something I
saw people have stolen 200 cows they
enter a certain gate and you can't see
the cows and the people 200
Then one of my friends when you teach
the kingdom some of these things will
not happen
book.
Seven points about warfare.
You can't teach warfare if you don't
have marks of victory.
I
know that after I had a dream in a car
in a car in a carapus
Tell your neighbor alter.
So number one there must be uncut wood.
Why? Because human effort is not needed
here.
The second thing the effort of a man is
to now prepare is to carry the wood.
Carry the wood.
Arrange the wood on the altar.
But an altar without a sacrifice is a
monument.
So there must be a sacrifice.
And anything that is released on the
altar in the patterns of the old needed
blood
because the real of the spirit does not
answer to currency.
It answers to blood.
That is the conversation of spirits.
Now you know for you to understand
spirituality the one that has been
demonstrated for long
tends to take the order of the day. So
what happens when a man goes to a strong
man, a witch, a wizard, whoever he is, a
sorcerer, they will always ask
something, what do you want us to do for
you? and you go and say I want to be
rich in Leuru. By the time you mention
rich, they know they need to summon the
spirit of Mammon.
In the occultic and demonic, there are
things they call sieges. A siege is like
a password that you enter to summon a
certain spirit.
And for that spirit to answer, it
doesn't come by a siege only. A siege. A
good example of a siege. When the young
people were doing the chaly chaly
challenge, they will draw some circles
and something like an X and then they
will shout. Now that's a siege.
It's a demonic pattern that is connected
to a certain spirit. So there's many
password. So the more passwords you
know, the more sieges you know and your
capacity in the spirit is what gives you
power in the demonic because the more
demons you can summon the more powerful
you become because if I need to summon
the demon of wealth mmon he comes. If I
need to summon the demon of anarchy um
bleal he comes. So I don't need the help
of another priest. I just need to know
by this siege and by this altar and the
this sacrifice ble will come. There's a
time there were processes in town and I
was praying the lord told me the spirit
released is called bial. It is the
spirit of anarchy and chaos. Is there in
the bible where the bible says you
cannot you cannot be unequally yolked
with bleal. The word there is not an
unbeliever is a violent man. Belal it's
a demon.
Now so the man will lay his altar do his
enchantments
and provoke it and that's why now
someone will tell you what you have
asked for look for a black goat
because the demand of the spirit you
want me to summon must answer to the
blood of this thing.
So that's the language of spirits.
Now Jesus
knowing what it means hey
could not go without leaving us with
blood
because now you cannot survive with the
blood of bulls.
That technology
is for the devil.
you you can only survive by the living
ancient blood of Yeshua.
So what will they do? Because when you
look at the pattern, you understand our
biblical spirituality. Whatever happens
in the demonic, the patterns are
borrowed. So what they do, they will now
give speech to the blood. They will give
speech to the blood
and say now uh this man wants to finish
pastor T. We want to release the spirit
of bleal in the church. So the church
will enter into anarchy. No one will
ever obey him. Accusation will enter. So
we are not just releasing ble. We're
releasing leviadan. Accusations will
enter and within two months there will
be no church. Boo releases his and gives
speech. Pastor T fall.
So spirits have been dispatched and you
begin to see members instead of coming
for prayer they in small circles saying
change
and then gossips then boom the church
dies if nothing happens. Now if they do
that I don't need to go and look for a
bigger bull
and look for a bigger witch and
then tell him now
[Music]
that is witchcraft
and the paradox and the controversy is
that bull can work.
It's called the law of cancellation but
not nullification.
So when they discover you have given a
bull and they go and give two bulls,
your sacrifice is canled. Now you are
back to warfare. So now you need to go
with five bulls. How many bulls will you
give?
And now
what has now been taught in church is
they gave a bigger sacrifice.
You need a bigger sacrifice. The day
they will outgive your sacrifice, your
battles will be back
and they they have intelligence. They
can discern when you have engaged.
Warfare arrows can be hard so they can
know this man has gone to an altar. He
has engaged and even some witches will
tell you where he has gone is more
powerful. consult a higher order. Now
the blood of Jesus kaya
is number one when they slaughter a bull
that blood has the lifespan of two days
it's not fresh what speaks is fresh
blood the blood of Jesus in the realms
of the spirit is the highest
no one can slaughter Jesus on the altar
so no matter what they slaughter it can
never reach the one that was slaughtered
for me. So all you need to do when you
hear they have slaughtered four bulls,
go and hold the four corners of the
whole of the of the altar of Calvary and
say the blood that speaketh better
things than the blood of bulls. Now
speak against the four bulls because you
are above bulls. This is the blood of
Yeshua, the Lord, the one that was shed
2,000 years ago. Let the speech of that
blood speak over my life and leave an
offering of thanksgiving and go home.
Don't wait to vibrate
to feel fire
by faith. You believe this book.
Well, how did you get born again? You
believe that Jesus died for you. Why was
he dying? One of the operations was to
leave you with his blood. So you are not
a believer without advantage.
Is someone hearing me? And so there are
people who have been surviving pastor.
[Music]
And now we keep you in a system of
witchcraft called cancellation. What
does the blood of Jesus do? It
nullifies.
It does not cancel. It nullifies the
agenda of that altar. And guess what?
Not only does it nullify, it also now
covers you and protects you. That even
if they go back, their altar can never
work. I want to declare to somebody in
this house, there is another altar that
is more powerful than anything that they
could have ever raised against your
life. What do I need, pastor? Only
believe.
>> Only believe.
only believe. We went to Kindi
get in lu
they take our photos
and is put in their island
and the doctors in the land went and
took two goats.
One was written my name. The other one
was written the name of the host.
Slaughtered them and threw them in the
sea
to cast our meeting.
I just made a small prayer.
Blood of Jesus speak over my life and
over the meeting. We did the meeting.
People got born again. By that sea I was
taken to the airport.
I felt like telling them, "How can you
waste
water
in the sea?
The day you overcome your fear
or frustrate your fear is the day your
faith will mature.
Am I speaking to anyone?
Tell your neighbor neighbor
character development.
Hallelujah. So all you just do is give a
thanksgiving because you can't raise
another altar and we'll come to
understand what we call unconditional
covenant whereby it is God who has done
it for you. You don't need to do it for
yourself. So all you do is identify with
what he has done. But you see the
problem with men because of our
background in terms of witchcraft and
all that. We we always believe it cannot
be so
let the blood speak over your life. Evil
[Music]
connect. Tell your neighbor too.
There's no complication.
So
an altar and by I'm going slowly because
I know we are many of us and I want even
those who are young in the faith to also
catch up. Let me let me begin to wind
up. There are three things on the altar.
Number one, there is a stone, there is
the wood and then there is the
sacrifice. Are you getting it? There is
the sacrifice.
The work of the fire was not the work of
God. I mean it was not the work of the
man. When the sacrifice was accepted,
what happened is that heaven consumed it
with a fire. Leviticus chapter number
6:12
and and and verse 13.
Leviticus 6:12 and verse 13. I want to
show you.
And the fire on the altar shall be kept
burning on it. It shall not be put out.
And the priest shall burn wood on it
every morning, and lay the burnt
offering in order it. And he shall burn
on it the fat of the peace offering.
See? See? A a fire shall always be
burning. Look at the next one. A fire
shall always be burning on the altar. It
shall never go out. Do you know what
this means?
It was the work of the man to raise an
altar, put the wood, release the
sacrifice, but it was the work of God to
release the fire. But it was also the
work of man to sustain the fire. So how
do you sustain the fire? By more wood
and more sacrifice.
So if the fire goes out, it means we now
need another encounter because that fire
when God lit it, it was not supposed to
go out. There was a Levite at night to
add wood. And it was not the work of
Levites to bring the sacrifice. It was
the children of Israel who brought the
sacrifice to the Levite. But the work of
the Levite is to bring wood. So what did
the Levite do? He raised an altar, put
the wood on in order. The work of the
people was to bring the sacrifice. The
work of God was to bring the fire. The
work of the Levite and the people was to
make sure the Levite adds more wood and
the people add more sacrifice. That is
what keeps the fire.
>> Let me give you another scripture.
Chronicles chapter number 7 and verse
three.
2 Chronicles chapter number 7 and verse
one.
[Music]
When Solomon had finished praying,
fire came down from heaven and consumed
the burnt offering and the sacrifices
and the glory of the Lord filled the
temple. You can see the pattern. It came
down from heaven. What did it consume?
Not the stones.
The stones don't attract fire. It is the
sacrifice on the altar. Look at another
scripture finally.
1 Chronicles 21 and 26. 1 Chronicles 21
and 26.
1 Chronicles 21 and 26. And David built
there what? An altar to the Lord. What
did he do? And offered burnt offering
and peace offering and called on the
Lord. See how the Lord answered. And he
answered him from heaven by what? By
fire on the altar of burnt. What does
the fire look for? A sacrifice.
Romans chapter number 12 and verse one.
Romans 12 and verse one. Romans 12 and
verse one. What will bring back the fire
of God? This is the New Testament
sacrifice. I beseech you therefore,
brethren, by the mercies of God, what do
you do? That you present your bodies a
living sacrifice. Number one, there is a
condition. Holy. Number two, acceptable
to God. Number three, this is your
reasonable service. So why is indeed
that there is no fire? Holiness has has
es escaped. So the whatever is on the
altar is not acceptable. So the holy
fire cannot consume a defiled sacrifice.
Acts chapter number one.
You'll never disconnect revivals with
holiness.
That's why we have many people teaching
revival.
Very few manifesting.
Beginning from verse 23, Acts 1:23.
And they proposed to Joseph called
Barnabas, who was a name justice and
Matias. And they prayed and said, "You,
oh Lord, who knows the heart of all,
show which of the two you have chosen to
take part in the ministry and apostilhip
from which Judas by transgression fell
that he might go to the place and they
cast their lots and the lot fell on
Matias and he was numbered with 11."
A complete altar needs 12 stones.
In Acts chapter number one, we have to
build an altar.
for the fire in Acts chapter number two
to come.
Now the altar of Acts chapter number
one, it is not an altar of dead stones.
Is an altar of living stones.
The selection of the man
complete the number of stones needed.
There is nowhere else the man is
mentioned
in the spirit. The man that took over
Judas was Paul.
But we need Acts two because Damascus is
far because we need fire.
So let us gather 11 stones
but one is lacking. Let us pray to know
between these two stones Joseph and the
other one which is the stone. Pick it.
added to the 12. Now we have an altar.
Not only are these 11 the altar, but
they are the also the sacrifice.
So they have to prepare themselves as
the stones and cut. They must also lay
themselves as the altar. When the fire
came, anything that was on that altar
was consumed. We call it Pentecost.
Hey,
so Pentecost was beyond an event. It was
a fulfillment of the ancient pattern.
And then on Thursday, I will teach on
this. Let me have seven people stand
here.
Seven.
1 2 3 4 5 6 7
Can come. Those are seven. These are
called seven candlestands.
Now,
Pentecost,
the fire has fallen on the altar.
Men have been set on fire.
But the picture of the church is not
symbolized
by
Pentecost is symbolized by the minora in
revelation
because the Bible says there are seven
candlests but there are also seven
churches in Asia Minor
and all these candles must be on fire.
Follow kindly,
Ken. This is the altar of Pentecost.
Pick it. Set the church of Ephesus on
fire.
Prophetically, just look like you're
picking fire.
Set peach on fire. And then pe you lift
up your hands. You must catch fire.
Let me come down.
Let me show you what used to happen. So
the high priest when he wants to light
the minora, he will take his stick, go
to the altar. What is this altar? The
fire that is there is the fire of God,
not of a man. Then take the fire, light
the first candlestick,
light the second,
the third, the fourth, the fifth, the
sixth, and the seventh.
The pattern of revival is very simple
that there must be a priest who can
light this generation
and pass over the fire to the next.
light the next set the generation on
fire. It is not this priest lighting the
next.
But it is the fire that was with Paul
that is needed in the next church. So by
the time we are coming to the revival
Kenya is waiting for, it must look like
the revival Paul and
it cannot be that our revival is full of
dancers whereas theirs was full of
intercessors.
It cannot be our revival is full of DJs
where their intercessors I mean their
meetings were full of prophets. It
cannot be that our revival the church
has become a cool place. It is a seeker
sensitive. We go and massage you. But in
the fast men were cut in their hearts
when Peter was preaching. It can be get
the first fire.
>> This is where the error was. There's a
generation shouting revival. But what
they are failing to understand, they
have refused to study what gave birth to
that fire on the altar. Who shall repair
the altar? Who shall release himself as
a living sacrifice on the altar? Who
shall be the priest to make sure that
I'm not giving you a strange fire?
>> Because you can set a generation on a
strange fire where they go for aobics in
the name of praise the whole night.
Strange fire
miracle. I met one of the generals. He
told me
[Music]
why because there there is a lot of Can
I tell you something? Majority of many
young people coming up in ministry, they
have made the church to look like a very
cool place.
Memorial
generation die. Every day we are losing
many to depression, suicide because you
can't give a suicidal believer junk.
>> They need strong meat. They need
perception, change of reality. They need
genuine encounters.
A father told me the child went to one
of our camps.
Tell your neighbor, neighbor,
>> we must go back to the days of Paul. The
days of Peter, study what they knew.
If they never taught demons, they taught
Jes. Let's teach Jesus.
If they never taugh taught witches,
let's teach Jesus.
>> There is one witch called the witch of
Samaria.
Witch of Samaria. The story does not end
there. He got born again. The story does
not end there. He was delivered by
Peter.
So for me, that's what is important.
[Music]
Your message.
Am I preaching 21? There is no fire if
there is no sacrifice. There is no
continuation of fire if we cannot have
custodians of that fire. And that's why
my generation is saying all the fathers
are not passing over the mantle. It's
not a mantle. They can't pass when
alignment is wrong. You don't pray. You
don't do you don't labor in the word.
Your church looks like a joke. Yes, it
is young people, but radicalize them.
The world is training when the church is
entertaining. They can be on fire. Some
of them where they are going, they can't
dance now.
>> They need to be equipped. They will not
have time to come to church. In a few
years, they will be all over the globe
doing business. So, they can't dance
now. Something radical must happen. Can
you stand up on your feet? Tell that
neighbor, "Neighbor, we need a fast
fire." Tell that neighbor, "Neighbor, we
need a fast fire."
release your life as a living sacrifice
on the altars of Elohim. Hallelujah. I
want you to lift up your hand and just
begin to tell the Lord, baptize me with
a fresh fire. I am tired of an ordinary
life. Where I am going, I cannot go like
this. Where I am entering, I cannot
enter like this. Please don't get tired.
In 2 minutes, we must push prayer. We
have to push prayer. There is a place
you are going. There are certain realms
you must enter. You can't enter in your
your now level. There are certain
operations that are needed in your life.
There are certain doors that cannot open
with your now level. There must be a
release of fire.
[Music]
I am the stone. I am the one on the
altar. I pour my life as a living
sacrifice. I release myself to you
Elohim. If you are seeking for a man to
partner with, I am available. We declare
the fire will not go out in our
generation. The fire won't go out. We
will not compromise on the standards of
eternity. Life church liuru I declare
the fire of God will begin to be
released. It was men in Pentecost,
ordinary men, ordinary fishermen that
became global evangelist. Let the fire
move again. Let the fire move again. Let
the altar, let the altar be filled with
sacrifice. Let the altar be filled with
wasted men. people that are saying,
"Lord, I pour my life. I release myself.
Nothing shall hold me from praying, from
serving, from worshiping you.
an abandoned altar. They repaired the
altar. They set the wood on the altar.
They poured the water. He called upon
the name of the Lord from the place of
covenant. The God of Jacob, the God of
Israel, the God of Isaac, the God of
Abraham. He is a covenant keeping God.
Call him from the dimensions of
covenant. Call him from the dimensions
of covenant.
Don't get tired. In the next 2 minutes
begin to grow your capacity in the
spirit. Let that weight, let the fatigue
of prayer, let it begin to live your
life.
The men that attracted fire, they were
wasted on the altar. They were holy men
contend with anything that is contending
against you. Every defiling spirit, let
it leave your life. Every addiction,
every yoke, every idea, every thought,
whatever defiles you, let it not find a
let it not find a habitation.
Somebody pray. Somebody pray. Somebody
pray. There must be fire on my altar.
There must be fire on my life. Witches
cannot take me out. Demonic powers
cannot take me out. Let the blood begin
to speak over my life. People that are
going through warfare.
[Music]
Let me receive the worshippers. I want
to make a prayer. I want to make a
prayer. I want to make a prayer. And it
is only a people they there. I sense
this in my spirit. I want to break some
warfars today. I want to break some
warfars today. You have been on a long
pathway of warfare tied to a demonic
altar, witchcraft, sorcery, and all
that. Run to the altar. We are going to
declare the blood of Yeshua. Something
must be broken today. You have been on a
pathway of a long warfare. Long warfare.
Long warfare. Run to the altar.
Something must be broken today.
Something must be broken today. I don't
know where your name has been written.
Where they have laid your name, but
today by the authority and the fire of
the living God, something must come upon
you. Something must come upon you.
We do not rely on horses and chariots.
Our trust is in the Lord. Our trust is
in the Lord. The command of the armies
of heaven is the one that is going to
intervene over that matter.
When you come here, begin to pray. Begin
to pray. Begin to call upon the Lord.
Apply the blood of Jesus, call upon the
name of the Lord. The Bible says them
that call upon the name of the Lord,
they shall be delivered. Deliverance is
coming upon you. Healing is coming upon
you. Restoration is coming upon you.
Restoration
May the Lord May the Lord May the Lord
intervene. May the Lord fight for you.
May the Lord I see Chario. I see Chario.
Some of you the battle you are fighting
is the battle of Charios. Is the battle
of Charios. I declare in the name of
Jesus. Let the Lord intervene.
Contel,
[Music]
[Applause]
nalify, break, approve. Bring them down.
Bring them down.
There has been another priesthood in
your father's house.
[Music]
Let the blood speak over my life.
People that have shed blood because of
my career, because of my marriage and my
family.
Lord, you are the one that can happen
for me. Lord arise.
Let your blood speak over my mother. Let
your blood speak over my life. Let the
long battle come to an end. Let the
siege come to an end. Let the contention
come to an end. Let the attacks come to
an end. I stand on my altar.
are there. I stand on the altars of
Calvary. I stand by the rivers of the
blood, by the fountains of the blood. I
stand beside the rib cage of Yeshua. Let
the blood speak over my life. Let the
blood let the blood that came from
Emmanuel's vein. Let it contend for me.
Let it contend for me. Fire of God, let
it be upon my life.
Every fire that is against your life,
arrows that have been deployed, I see
altars going on fire, judgment over
every altar raised against your family.
[Music]
There is fire on my altar.
There is victory. I see chariots
retreating. I see fire falling on altars
to chart and to consume. I see the sword
of vengeance being lifted on your
behalf. The Lord that fights our
battles. May he arise. May he arise. May
he arise. Anyone that marked you today
in the name of Jesus, we reverse the
arrow.
[Music]